[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the chinchilla classified according to the peak of its activeness throughout the day?", "correct_answer": "Crepuscular", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Nocturnal", "Duirnal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Middle Ages, the purple color was used only for royal clothing because the dye was much more expensive than gold. What was the purple dye made from?", "correct_answer": "Mollusk", "incorrect_answers": ["Chocolate", "squid Ink", "Violets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Benchwarmers from the self-titled movie play with how many Little League teams?", "correct_answer": "9", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "13", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the word ecology, which derives from Greek?", "correct_answer": "study of the household", "incorrect_answers": ["study of life", "None of these", "study of nature"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie stars George Peppard as a WWI ace pilot?", "correct_answer": "The Blue Max", "incorrect_answers": ["The Blue Baron", "The Red Baron", "The Black Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The acouchis, small diurnal rodents found along riverbanks in the Amazon Rainforest, usually feed on this type of food.", "correct_answer": "Fruit", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "Grass", "Nuts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The film The Legend of Boggy Creek was the tale of this creature.", "correct_answer": "The Fouke Monster", "incorrect_answers": ["Abominable Swampman", "The Creek Thing", "Arkansas Beast"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This intricate name, given to water, is a common hoax to misleadingly present water as a dangerous and harmful compound.", "correct_answer": "Dihydrogen monoxide (DHMO)", "incorrect_answers": ["Decaborane", "Diborane", "Disilane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the move Superman Returns, what did Lois Lanes fiance Richard enjoy doing.", "correct_answer": "piloting a seaplane", "incorrect_answers": ["acting", "racecar driving", "trying to chase Superman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1987, this designer received an Oscar for Best Foreign Designer from the Council of Fashion Designers of America, and later the same year, he opened his own couture house in Paris.", "correct_answer": "Lacroix", "incorrect_answers": ["Chanel", "Valentino", "Dior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turkeys are named after the country of Turkey.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the card game Magic: The Gathering, if your opponent casts Rend Flesh at your Hand of Honor, which spell could you use to save your creature?", "correct_answer": "Ghostway", "incorrect_answers": ["Ebony Owl Netsuke.", "Stifle", "Oblivion Stone"]}]